admanage.com 2018-12-16

# Pay Per Click, Keyword Targeted CPC Text Banner & XML Search Feeds Affiliate Privacy Policy

Admanage SA (AdManage) is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using any of our online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we receive when you transmit data to any machine owned by AdManage.

## Web Form Information

When you submit information to AdManage to make a payment or open an account, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, email address, credit card number. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen.

## Web Site Usage Information

We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each web page, and the length of their visits.

## How We Use Information Collected

**We may use information in the following ways:**

  * For the purposes you specifically provided the information including, for example, enabling us to process, validate and verify purchases.
  * To register you as a client and establish an account for you.
  * To send you email notifications about our new or existing AdManage products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.
  * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.
  * To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.
  * To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.
  * To allow 3rd party companies to send the client emails promoting other goods and services.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so.

## Cookies

We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. AdManage employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This information enables us to deliver faster service to our subscribers, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All AdManage cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to AdManage web servers, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information.

## Security

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us.

## In Partnership with AppNexus

Admanage has partnered with AppNexus for the purposes of display ad serving, as well as an exchange to buy and sell traffic within. Please note that with regards to purchasing or selling display traffic, the AppNexus Privacy Policy, in addition to the Admanage Privacy Policy will apply.

[Click here](http://appnexus.com/platform-policy) to review the AppNexus Privacy Policy.

## Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.

## Comments and Questions

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us through the contact page.
